A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Organizational and Employment History, Accession 2018:041 FA743
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Staff Biographies and Directories, 1953-2008; 3; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
  - Staff Bios - "Mc", 1955-2002 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    McDermott, John V.
    McDonald, Bernard
    McDonald, David T.
    McGrath, John Williams
    McGruder, Karen B.
    McGurk, Stephen J.
    McHenry, Donald F.
    McKay, Donald
    McKee, Donald
    McKee, Katherine W.
    McKeever, Porter
    McLaughlin, Robert T.
    McLean, Mora L.
    McLean, Sheila Avrin
    McLean, Vincent J.
    McNamara, Robert Strange
    McNayr, Irving G.
    McNichols, Steven E.
    McNown, John S.
    McPeak, William Wallace
    McQueeney, Patrick
    McShane, Mary
    McVicker, Charles P.
  - Staff Bios - "M", 1957-2004 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Magat, Richard
    Magrath, Katherine B.
    Mahoney, Richard T.
    Malina, Wendy
    Maloney, Alice L.
    Manitzas, Nita R.
    Mann, Lori J.
    Manus, Mara
    Marcelo, Alexandrina B.
    Marks, Stephen P.
    Marsh, Betsey V.
    Marshall, Dorothy Nepper
    Marshall, Jonathan
    Martin, Courtney
    Martin, Julie
    Martus, Marjorie
    Masone,, Nunzio Jr.
    Massack, George M.
    Mathews, Betty P.
    Matters, Clyde B.
    Matthews, Harvey B.
    Mavity, Jane Hinchcliffe
    May, Oliver
    Mayer, Robert Anthony
    Mazon Jeffers
    Raquel Mazon
    Mead, Leonard C.
    Meade, Edward J., Jr.
    Measham, Anthony R.
    Megally, Hanny
    Meilink, Harry F.
    Menan, Nancy V.
    Mensah, Lisa
    Menzies, Nicholas K.
    Merillat, H. C. L.
    Mertens, Walters M.
    Meyer, Pamela M.
    Miao, Jean Theresa
    Millard, Stanley R.
    Miller-Travis, Vernice
    Miller, Anita Miller
    Miller, Frank Joseph
    Miller, Joan R.
    Miller, Joseph Irwin
    Miller, Seymour M.
    Miller, Thomas F.
    Miller, Paul F., Jr.
    Millikan, Parnie
    Milliken, William G.
    Millner, Natalie
    Mina, Maria A.
    Miranda, Gloria
    Misra, Geetanjali
    Mister, Melvin A.
    Mistretta, Sandy S.
    Mitchell, Bert N.
    Mitchell, James Robert
    Mitchell, Kathryn
    Mitchell, Ralph, Jr.
    Mitchelson, Michael
    Mogensen, Wagn A.
    Mohamed, Inca A.
    Molnar, Janice M.
    Molter, Elizabeth D.
    Moore, Frank J.
    Moore, Richard Vance
    Moore, William J.
    Mooring, Shawn
    Moos, Malcolm C.
    Morrill, James L.
    Morrill, Thomas W.
    Morse, Richard M.
    Motley, Susan
    Moulton, Robert H.
    Moy, Kirsten
    Moyo, Jonathan N.
    Muecke, Marjorie A.
    Mullarkey, Michael J.
    Mundigo, Axel I.
    Munford, David C.
    Munn, Robert
    Murombedzi, James Christopher
    Murphy, Hugh T.
    Murphy, Judith Pequignot
    Myers, Robert G.
    Myntti, Cynthia
    Myrus, Donald R.
  - Staff Bios - "N", 1953-2005 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    Nachtigal, Paul
    Nadeau, Therese Edna
    Nagel, John S.
    Nasr, Salim
    Ndebele, Njabulo
    Nellis, John R.
    Nelson, Barbara
    Nelson, Courtney A.
    Nelson, Gordon O.
    Nelson, Lester W.
    Nelson, Michael
    Netherton, John P.
    Newman, Susan T.
    Newmann, John M.
    Newton, Quigg, Jr.
    Nicely, James M.
    Nicholson, Stanley Alan
    Nielsen, Waldemar
    Nims, William H.
    Nobbe, Catherine
    Nolan, Frederick J.
    Norgaard, Richard B.
    Northrop, Eugene Purdy
    Noyes, Ann W.
  - Staff Bios - "O", 1958-2003 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    O'Connell, Donald W.
    O'Connor, Charles Robert
    O'Hara, Elizabeth M.
    O'Mara, JoAnn
    Obasanjo, General Olusegun
    Ocasio, Linda
    Offenheiser, Raymond C.
    Ogata, Sadako
    Ogren, Lynn
    Oleon, Sally J.
    Olson, Jeffrey T.
    Olson, Peter
    Olson, Thomas F.
    Onwuachi-Saunders, Chukwudi Chu Chu
    Oppenheimer-Nicolau, Siobhan
    Oppenheimer, Joan-Ann
    Ore-Aguilar, Gaby
    Orzo, Joseph P.
    Osborn, Dorothy J.
  - Staff Bios - "P", 1955-2003 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    Page, Chris B.
    Pallotti, Marianne M.
    Palsrok, John
    Pande, Vijay G.
    Pariza, Helen B.
    Parker, Gordon H.
    Parker, Harrison
    Parvin, Fayette W.
    Paschal, Elizabeth
    Passin, Herbert
    Patterson, George
    Patterson, Laird D.
    Payton, Benjamin F.
    Pearson, Katharine
    Pearson, Paul B.
    Peirce, Margaret
    Pendleton, William C.
    Perkin, Gordon W.
    Perkins, Donald S.
    Perry, Ernest J.
    Petit, Michael
    Petricelli, John F.
    Pfanner, David E.
    Phillips, Theresa F.
    Picken, Margaret (Margo) M.
    Pincus, William
    Pistone, Vincent F.
    Plante, Lilian D.
    Plaxico, James
    Plesser, Nancy J.
    Plimpton, Jane F.
    Pope, James S.
    Poppe, S. Penney
    Porter, Leslie V.
    Porter, Willis P.
    Portes, Alejandro
    Posch, Eileen A.
    Potash, Ellen
    Potlow, Michele
    Powers, Brian M.
    Powers, Robert J.
    Preiskel, Barbara Scott
    Prescott, Kenneth W.
    Prezelski, Frank J.
    Price, Don Krasher
    Price, Stephen W.
    Prindle, Deborah
    Proscio, Anthony
    Provinse, John H.
    Pryce-Jones, Alan
    Pugh, George Douglas
    Pulsipher, Allan G.
    Puryear, Alvin N.
    Puryear, Jeffrey M.
    Pwono, Damien M.
  - Staff Bios - "Q", 1955-2002 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    Quan, Randy
    Quarles, Steven P.
    Quarmby, Andrew G.
    Quarmby, Diana
    Queener, Robert S.
    Quinn, John Anthony
  - Staff Bios - "R", 1958-2006 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Rabb, Harriett S.
    Racelis, Mary
    Radel, David
    Rae, Patricia Norris
    Ranis, Gustav
    Rao, K. Nagaraja
    Ray, Talton F.
    Redclift, Michael R.
    Reed, Ann T.
    Reed, Patricia Anne
    Reed, Richard S.
    Reed, William S.
    Reichstein, Marilyn
    Reid, Richard H.
    Remenyi, Joseph V.
    Renza, Paul T.
    Reynolds, John
    Reynolds, Lloyd G.
    Reynolds, Norman E.
    Reynolds, Richard B.
    Rice, Harold L.
    Riley, Robert E.
    Rimlinger, Gaston Victor
    Riolo, Anthony R.
    Risano, William F.
    Rivard, Alison
    Rizvi, S. A. Gowher
    Robarts, Richard C.
    Roberts, Richard S.
    Robin, John P.
    Robinson, Mark A.
    Robinson, Marshall A.
    Rodriguez-Lukas, Alice
    Rohling, Michael
    Roman, Ruth
    Romano, Frederick V. Jr.
    Romero, Anthony D.
    Romm, Jeffrey
    Ross, Gabrielle
    Rosser, K. Colin
    Roussel, Jennifer
    Row, Arthur T.
    Rowser, Sharon
    Roy, Delwin A.
    Rubinger, Michael
    Rudlin, Walter Arthur
    Ruff, Larry E.
    Runningwater, Niles Bird
    Ruof, Peter
    Rutherford, Robert E.
    Ryan, Leonard Eames
  - Staff Bios - "S", 1953-2004 (Box 7, Folder 62-63)
    Saario, Terry N.
    Sadowski, Katherine
    Sage, Joan
    Saich, Anthony J.
    Saint,, William S.
    Salacuse, Jeswald W.
    Sale, William Barnett
    Saltzman, Henry
    Sameulson, Judith F.
    Samuelson, Paul R.
    Sandberg, Donald Francis
    Sanders, Irwin Taylor
    Sandville, Jonathan
    Santos, John F.
    Santos, John Phillip
    Sarraf, Laurice H.
    Saudek, Robert
    Saulniers, Suzanne Smith
    Saunders, Lyle
    Sayward, Nick
    Scaller, Howard G.
    Scanlon, John Joseph
    Scatena, Elisa M.
    Schacht, Henry B.
    Schachter, Esther Roditti
    Schaeffer, Sheldon F.
    Scher, Vicki A.
    Schiff, Arthur
    Schleck, Mary Louise
    Schmid, Robert Carl
    Schoenfield, Paul J.
    Schrank, Robert
    Schull, Joseph
    Schuman, Barry R.
    Schutjer, Wayne Alan
    Schuyler, George Warren
    Schwarz, Ralph G.
    Sciortino, Rosalina M.
    Sconyers, Nancy
    Scott, Thomas D.
    Seaver, Robert C.
    Seay, George L.
    Seckler, David W.
    Seessel, Thomas V.
    Sellers, Patricia
    Seltzer, Michael S.
    Shapiro, Irving S.
    Shaplin, Judson
    Shaplin, Marjorie
    Sharpe, Richard
    Shaughnessy, Bill
    Shavers, Juanita
    Shaw, Robert d'A
    Shcherby, Stefan
    Shearer, Eleanor
    Sheldon, Richard C.
    Shepard, Bonnie
    Shimmel, Gilbert
    Shorter, Frederic C.
    Shroeder, Mary H.
    Shuh, C. Edward
    Sidel, Mark
    Sidford, Holly
    Silj, Alessandro
    Silvert, Kalman Hirsch
    Simmons, Ozzie G.
    Simmons, Reuben
    Simoni, Carl D.
    Simons, Hans
    Singer, Norman J.
    Skapski, Adam
    Skolnick, Betty P.
    Slater, Gerald
    Slater, Joseph E.
    Slater, Joseph Elliott
    Sloane, Margaret N.
    Smith, Anna Deavere
    Smith, Bradford
    Smith, Donald Borden
    Smith, Joshua Lawrence
    Smith, LeRoy O.
    Smith, Michael
    Smith, Robb E.
    Smith, Roger M.
    Smith, Theodore M.
    Smock, David R.
    Smuckler, Ralph H.
    Socknat, James A.
    Soedjatmoko, Dr.
    Sohn, Gigi
    Sommer, John G.
    Sonenblum, Michele R.
    Southam, Anna L.
    Spadafora, Jo-Una
    Spahn, Kathleen L.
    Spangenberg, Gail
    Spearman, Dianne E.
    Speir, Robert Wade
    Spencer, Edson W.
    Spencer, James
    Spencer, John
    Spencer, Sarah
    Spilka, Leonard S.
    Spoelberch, Guillaume de
    Stanley, Peter
    Staples, Eugene S.
    Stathes, George H.
    Stedman, Eugene S.
    Steele, Jen Louise
    Steibert, Catherine
    Stein, Ellen Robin
    Steingruebner, Gertrude
    Stephansky, Ben S.
    Stern, Lynn
    Stevens, Ross
    Stevenson, Clinton L.
    Stevenson, James H.
    Stewart-Hill, Anne Bohen
    Stewart, Charles A.
    Stewart, Donald Mitchell
    Stickler, Izaak M.
    Stiver, John J.
    Stivers, Jerrold L.
    Stoddard, Alexander J.
    Stoller, Ezra
    Stone, John R.
    Stone, Shepard
    Stone, Lester M.
    Stoup, Louella
    Strasburg, Paul A.
    Strasma, John D.
    Stratton, Catherine Nelson
    Stratton, Julius Adams
    Strumpf, Linda B.
    Stucky, Conrad C.
    Stuhldreher, Anne Catherine
    Sucherman, Stuart F.
    Suehsdorf, Adolph III
    Sullivan, Oona
    Sutija, George
    Sutter, John
    Sutton, Francis X.
    Suwannarat, Gary S.
    Sviridoff, Mitchell
    Swayzee, Cleon Oliphant
    Swearer, Howard R.
    Sweeney, Edward B.
    Sweeney, William O.
    Szanton, David Lawrence
  - Staff Bios - "T", 1953-2007 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    Tantillo, Frank
    Tatti, Adele R.
    Taylor, Andrea
    Taylor, Elizabeth P.
    Teitelbaum, Michael S.
    Tenny, Barron M.
    Teper, Shirley
    Tesdell, Kerwin
    Tharan, Caridad Sri
    Thery, Jane L. Barber
    Thomas-Inniss, Marjorie E.
    Thomas, Dorothy
    Thomas, Franklin A.
    Thomas, Frederic C.
    Thomas, Rita L.
    Thomas, Robert L.
    Thompson, Cliff F.
    Thompson, Marcia T.
    Thompson, Probyn Jr.
    Thornhill, Kenneth J.
    Thrash, Ernestine
    Thurber, Clarence E.
    Tickton, Sidney G.
    Tierney, James T.
    Tillett, Anthony D.
    Tobias, George
    Toksoz, Sadik
    Tolles, Robert E.
    Tolley, Howard Ross
    Tosterud, Robert
    Trager, Lillian
    Trautman, De Forest L.
    Travers, S. Lee
    Tropeano, Louise
    Trowbridge, James W.
    Turner, J. Michael
    Turner, Joe Coburn
  - Staff Bios - "U", 1971-2007 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    Ubinas, Luis A.
    Umphrey, Susan Goodwillie
    Urquhart, Brian
  - Staff Bios - "V", 1965-2008 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    Van Buskirk, Ann G.
    Sheila Nelson
    Van Duzer, Doris A.
    van Leeuwen, Robert J.
    Van Wyk, Menno H.
    Vargas-Adams, Emily
    Vasquez, Blanca R.
    Veblen, Eric
    Veneable, Dawanna
    Venezian, Eduardo L.
    Ventilla, Martha
    Verost, Patricia
    Villard, Henry H.
    Volkman, Toby
    von Stoephasius, Renata
  - Staff Bios - "W", 1955-2007 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Wadia, Anna S.
    Wadsworth, Homer C.
    Wagner, Lewis E.
    Wald, Pat Walker, Mary Lynn
    Walker, Ronald P. Walker, W. Hugh
    Walsh, M. Patricia
    Walsh, Nina C. Wang, David Ward, F. Champion
    Ward, Haskell George Warden, Annette Warden, Charles B. Wasow, Bernard Watkins, Lucy R. Watson, Andrew Watson, Clarence E. Watterson, Libby Watts, Glenn E. Watts, William Weber, Gerard J.
    Webber, James B. Jr. Webster, Bethuel Weekes, Richard V. Weisblat, Abraham M. Weiss, John K. Weldon, Peter D. Welna, Christopher Wheaton, Diane M.
    White, Betty B. Whiting, Basil J. Jr. Whitney, Joseph B. R.
    Whitney, W. Keith
    Wiatrak, Michael
    Wickham, Robert Saunderson Widdicombe,, Stacey Harrison Wiesner, Mary Ann Wilbur, Karl M. Wilde, Quirina Wiley, Walter B.
    Wilhelm, Harry E.
    Wilkins, Roger W.
    Williams, Joanna
    Williams, Richard D.
    Williams, Robert V. Wilson, Charles
    Wilson, John Stanton Wilson, Kenneth Wilson, L. Albert Winans, Edgar V.
    Winder, David Winnick, Louis
    Winnick, Roy
    Winquist, Gertrude
    Witty, Joanne Wolf, Alfred C. Wolf, Thomas W. Wolfe, Ronald Gary Wolters, Curt C. F. Wong, Gary D. Wong, Wayne F.
    Wood, Carlton L. Wood, Garland P. Wood, Shirley
    Woodman, Everett M. Woodring, Paul Worrall, Robert P. Wright, Thomas H. Jr. Wyllie, Ann P. Wyman, Thomas H. Wyzanski, Charles Edward Jr.
  - Staff Bios - "X, Y, Z", 1953-2003 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Yates, Stacie L.
    Ylvisaker, Paul Norman
    Young, Alicia
    Young, Ernest L.
    Young, Walter Lee
    Zabriskie, Peteer E.
    Zeidenstein, George
    Zeitlin, June H.
    Ziff, Charles E.
    Zimmerman, Nancy
    Zimmermann, R. Peter
    Zipkin, Carol A.
    Zwerling, L. Steven
  - Miscellaneous Staff Bios, 1993-2008 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    Falconer, Alsie
    Fachel Leal, Ondina
    Fraser, Gertrude
    Gaberman, Barry D.
    Gaddis, Maxine
    Geske, Aina
    Gray, Verna E.
    Green, Jonathan W.
    Gurung, Ashkok
    Hawes, Gary
    James, Angela
    Jenkins, Alan
    Jimenez, Norma
    Johnson, Marjorie E.
    Kanem, Natalia
    Krauskopf, Marian
    Lane, Robin
    Lapp, Sharon
    Lentz, Becky
    Loftus, Mary
    Lopez, Vivian A.
    Liu, Mina Titi
    Lurie, Theodora
    Mallee, Hein
    Malombe, Joyce
    Martin, Christopher
    Mathewson, Kevin M.
    McCutcheon, Aubrey
    Mehra, Rekha
    Messersmith, Lisa
    Miller, Douglas
    Montes, Manuel Butch
    Nikova, Natalia
    Okedi, William
    Oku, Julia
    Oliver, Angela L.
    Oliver, Melvin L.
    Olowo, Zipporah
    Opoku-Mensah, Aida
    Oppegard, Robert
    Owens, Millard Mitty
    Phillips, Barbara
    Pinnock, Julie R.
    Powell, Jennifer
    Powel Smith, Carol M.
    Quinn, Thomas M.
    Raj, Sushil
    Rakhmanova, Galina
    Ramaswamy, Sumathi
    Rhea, Janice L.
    Salole, Gerry
    Serotta, Donald L.
    Shapiro, Judith
    Sheehan, Brigid
    Smith, Bradford K.
    Smith, Marcia A.
    Soni, Rita
    Starke-Skinner, Odessa
    Tangredi, Robyn
    Vaid, Urvashi
    Varas, Augusto F.
    Wilde, Alexander
    Williams, Lorelei
    Wing, Christine
    Winters, David
    Yampolsky, Philip
    Yates, Elizabeth
    Zhou, John
    Zurbuchen, Mary S.
  - Staff Listing by Unit, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Staff Biographies, 1967 January (Box 8, Folder 71)
    Anderson, David A.
    Baldwin, Charles Stephen
    Bell, David E.
    Bell, Peter Dexter
    Bergman, Elihu
    Bloom, Clark Clarence
    Bohrson, Ralph G.
    Borgmann, Carl W.
    Bowles, Frank
    Boyce, Mary Alice
    Bracken, Kieran Michael
    Bresnan, John Joseph
    Bundy, McGeorge
    Bunker, Samuel Emmet
    Bunnell, Robert A.
    Bush, Evelyn C.
    Cantwell, Lawrence Robert
    Cooney, Thomas Edwin
    Crawley, Roy W.
    Crossland, Fred Eugene
    Curley, James Robert
    D'Arms, Edward Francis
    de Janosi, Peter Engel
    Dennis, Nancy W.
    Dressner, Howard Roy
    Dye, Richard Wilder
    Edley, Christopher Fairfield
    Erf, Herbert A.
    Fantini, Mario D.
    Farrell, James R.
    Feldman, Marvin Jack
    Felling, William Edward
    Ferguson, Alan Douglas
    Fox, Melvin James
    Fraenkel, Adolf Peter
    Friendly, Fred W.
    Gant, George Franklin
    Hanson, Haldore
    Hardy, James Douglas
    Haris, Bela M.
    Heap, David
    Hertz, Willard Joel
    Himes, James Robert
    Hofmann, Edward G.
    Hopkins, Richard Appleton
    Kangas, Lenni William
    LeMelle, Wilbert John
    Manitzas, Nita Rous
    Meade, Edward James
    Nagel, John Stephan
    Nelson, Courtney Andrew
    Pendleton,, William Clyde
    Plante, Lillian Dillon
    Renza, Paul Thomas
    Robarts, Richard Charles
    Sarraf, Laurice Helen
    Scott, Thomas Dunlop
    Sheldon, Richard Cheney
    Staples, Eugene Sheldon
    Stone, Lester Monroe
    Walker, W. Hugh
    Ward, F. Champion
    Watson, Clarence E.
    Watts, William
    Weber, Gerard J.
    Wickham, Robert Saunderson
    Widdicombe, Stacey Harrison
    Wilhelm, Harry Eugene
    Winnick, Louis Winnick
- Staff Pictures, undated; 3; 0.62 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 half-legal box
  - A, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
    Armsey, James Atwater, Verne S. Albrecht, H. R. Andronetti, R.
  - B, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
    Barker, E. G.
    Bell, David
    Borgman, Carl
    Bryant, J.
    Barry, Frank J.
    Baldwin, Stephen
    Bush, C.
    Bell, Peter
    Brezenoff, Stanley
    Boland, Mary
    Baldwin, S.
    Barone, Carol
    Bourne, Rosemary
    Bunker, S.
    Bloom, Carl
    Barber, Elinn
    Busman, John
  - C, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
    Catacano
    Carlson, David B., Jr.
    Crossland, Fred
    Chamberlain, Mariam
    Cooney, Thomas E.
    Cutler, Thomas M.
    Capozzi, Elsie
    Cotter, William
    Catalano, Richard
    Cantwell, Larry
    Corrigan, Pat
  - D, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
    Dressner, Howard
    D'Arms, E. F.
    Dye
    Dahl, N. C.
    Dennis, Nancy
    de Janosi, Peter
  - E, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
    Edley, Christopher
    Eduardo, Robert H.
  - F, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
    Fox, Melvin
    Feldman, M.
    Frankel, Peter
    Frank, Jane
    Forsberg, Ingum
    Farrell, Jane
    Fredericks, W.
    Finklestein, David
    Frodin, Reuben
    Fantini, Mario
  - G, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
    Gormbley, William
    Gant, George
    Gamble, William
    Guntkin, Davidson
    Gibb, Bruce
    Gordon, Stanley
  - H, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
    Hill, F. F.
    Hardin, Lowell
    Heaps
    Hall
    Hilliard, John
    Hermes, James
  - I, undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
    Ivy, James
  - K, undated (Box 9, Folder 81)
    Kohl, W.
    Kemp, Phil
    Kimbler, M.
    Kingsley, Donald
  - L, undated (Box 9, Folder 82)
    Lenagh, Thomas
    Lewis, B.
    Levin, F. G.
    Lowry, McNeil
  - M, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
    R. Magat; E. J. Meade, Jr.; William Moore; B. Mitchell; R. Mager; Manitas; M. Martas; Seymour M. Miller; Frank Joseph Miller
  - Mc, undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
    McNichols, S. E.
  - N, undated (Box 9, Folder 85)
    Nims, William
    Nelson, Courtney
    Nagel
    Netherton
    Nadeau, Therese
  - P, undated (Box 9, Folder 86)
    Perkin, Gordon
    Plante, L.
    Pfanner, D. E.
  - R, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
    Ryan, Leonard
    Robinson, Marshall
    Roberts, C.
    Rao
    Renza, Paul
  - S, undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
    Sheldon, M.
    Swearer, Howard
    Scanlon, John
    Sarraf, L.
    Sloane, M.
    Smith, Ted
    Schwarz, Ralph
    Staples, Eugene
    Smock, David
    Sontham, Anna
    Sandberg, D.
    Stewart, Donald
    Schiff
  - T, undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
    Trowbridge
    Thompson, P.
  - W, undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
    Winnick, Louis
    Wilkins, Roger
    Wilhelm, Harry
    Walker
    Whiting, Basil
    Watson, C. E.